<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>hexalate.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Hexalate</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Hexalate</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Hexalate</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Hexalate</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Hexalate</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Hexalate</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Hexalate</name>
  <name xml:lang="ms">Hexalate</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Hexalate</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Hexalate</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Hexalate</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Hexalate</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Hexalate</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Hexalate</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Hexalate</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh">Hexalate</name>
  <summary>Spin circles to match colors</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Otáčejte kruhy tak, aby se barvy shodovaly</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Drehen Sie Kreise, um Farben in Übereinstimmung zu bringen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Gire los círculos para hacer coincidir los colores</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Forgassa a köröket a színek illesztéséhez</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Sukite ratus, kad sutaptų spalvos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ms">Putar bulatan untuk padankan warna</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Draai cirkels om kleuren te koppelen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Obróć koła, aby dopasować kolory</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Rode os círculos para corresponder as cores</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Rode os círculos para combinar as cores.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Rotiţi cercurile pentru potrivirea culorilor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Вращайте круги, чтобы сопоставить цвета</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh">旋转圆盘以搭配颜色</summary>

  <description>
    <p>Hexalate is a color matching game. The goal of the game is to rotate and position the circles so that each touching line matches in color. You rotate circles by right clicking, and you move circles by dragging them. The game stores the positions and rotations of the circles across runs.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Hexalate ist ein Farbenrätsel. Ziel des Spiels ist es, die Kreise so zu drehen und zu positionieren, dass alle sich berührenden Linien die gleiche Farbe haben. Sie können die Kreise durch einen rechten Mausklick rotieren und durch Ziehen mit der Maus positionieren. Das Spiel merkt sich den Spielstand, wenn Sie es beenden und neu starten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Hexalate es un juego de coincidir colores. La meta del juego es rotar y posicionar los círculos para que cada línea próxima coincida en color. Rotas los círculos dando clic derecho, y mueves los círculos arrastrándolos. El juego almacena la posición y rotación de los círculos entre juegos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Hexalate egy színpárosító játék. A játék célja a körök forgatása és áthelyezése úgy, hogy minden érintkező vonal színben illeszkedjen. A köröket a jobb kattintással forgathatja, és húzással mozgathatja azokat. A játék eltárolja a körök pozícióit és forgatásait a futtatások között.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Hexalate yra spalvų sutapimo žaidimas. Žaidimo tikslas yra sukti ir nustatyti tokią ratų padėtį, kad kievienos susiliečiančios linijos spalva sutaptų. Jūs sukate ratus, spusteldami ant jų dešiniuoju pelės mygtukų, o tempdami - juos perkeliate. Paleidimo tarpais, žaidimas išsaugo ratų vietą ir pasukimą.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ms">Hexalate merupakan permainan padanan warna. Matlamat permainan adalah untuk putar dan letak semula bulatan supaya setiap bahagian sepadan warnanya. Anda boleh putar dengan mengklik kanan, dan anda boleh alih bulatan dengan menyeretnya. Permainan menyimpan kedudukan dan putaran bulatan sepanjang permainan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Hexalate is een kleurkoppelspel. Het doel is om de cirkels zo te draaien en te positioneren dat elke koppellijn dezelfde kleur heeft. Cirkels kun je draaien door te klikken met de rechtermuisknop en verplaatsen door ze te verslepen. Het spel slaat de positie en de rotaties van de cirkels tijdens het spel op.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Hexalate jest grą dopasowania kolorów. Celem gry jest obrócić i ustawić koła, tak aby ich linie były dopasowane do tych samych kolorów. Możesz obracać koła klikając prawym przyciskiem myszy i przenosić je przeciągnięciem myszy. Gra zapisuje pozycje i obroty kół przy następnym uruchomieniu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Hexalate é um jogo de correspondência de cores. O objetivo do jogo é rodar e posicionar os círculos para que cada linha que toque corresponda à cor da outra linha. Roda-se os círculos com o botão direito do rato e move-se os círculos arrastando-os. O jogo armazena as posições e rotações dos círculos entre execuções da aplicação.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Hexalate é um jogo de combinação de cores. O objetivo do jogo é rodar e posicionar os círculos para que cada linha seja combinada com as mesmas cores. Você roda os círculos apertando o botão direito do mouse, e move os círculos arrastando-os. O jogo guarda as posições e rotações dos círculos através das rodadas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Hexalate este un joc de potrivire a culorilor. Scopul jocului este de a roti şi poziţiona cercurile astfel încît fiecare linie care se atinge să se potrivească la culoare. Rotiţi cercurile cu clic dreapta, şi mutaţi cercurile prin glisarea acestora. Jocul stochează poziţiile şi rotaţiile cercurilor din întreaga rulare.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Hexalate - игра сопоставления цветов. Цель игры состоит в том, чтобы вращать и перемещать круги так, что бы каждый цветной луч касался другого луча такого же цвета. Круги можно вращать и перемещать правой кнопкой мыши. Игра сохраняет позиции кругов и можно продолжить играть при следующем запуске.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh">Hexalate 是一款颜色搭配游戏。游戏的目标是通过旋转和移动圆盘，使每一对接触的谱线颜色一致。单击以旋转圆盘，拖拽以移动圆盘。本游戏会保存上次退出时的圆盘位置和旋转情况。</p>
  </description>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://gottcode.org/hexalate/screenshots/appdata.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">https://gottcode.org/hexalate/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gottcode.org/hexalate/bugs/</url>
  <url type="donation">https://gottcode.org/tip/</url>
  <url type="translate">https://www.transifex.com/projects/p/hexalate/</url>

  <developer_name>Graeme Gott</developer_name>
  <update_contact>graeme@gottcode.org</update_contact>

  <translation type="qt">hexalate</translation>

  <provides>
    <binary>hexalate</binary>
  </provides>

  <kudos>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
  </kudos>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.0">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>

  <releases>
    <release version="1.1.2" date="2017-12-27">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>FIXED: Could not compile with Qt 5.10</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
